<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="h0745980bgefdfg4465g8fffg80a575ae040a" version="1">Archivist</content>
  <content contentuid="h3cabc88cgcc45g4811g96b6g6f202d38efa0" version="1">You've spent countless days in the preferred seclusion of libraries and archives, poring over the tomes within. You are particularly adept at reading, parsing, and copying someone else's work - and pay half price to copy Enchantment, Divination, and Conjuration spell scrolls. You also proficient in the Arcana and History skills.</content>
  <content contentuid="h843dd630gd578g4d0bga491gbd056065085a" version="1">Cartographer</content>
  <content contentuid="h6be30d02g328dg45d3ga627gb81e79c2a402" version="1">You were trained and employed in the exacting art of cartography. You know what plants grow where, the forgotten places of distant memories, and how to navigate terrain. You are proficient in Nature, History, and Survival. You have Advantage on Survival checks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4c7dbb44g5a1cg4356g828fgae4b6181329e" version="1">Courier</content>
  <content contentuid="hab76b7bag71e0g4f1bgb9d3g1ead7e7e283b" version="1">Working for your local postal service has taught you the value of being reliable, diligent, and timely. You are confident leading and riding animals, and are used to long days spent on your own feet, and can handle packages with discretion. You are proficient in Animal Handling, Athletics, and Stealth.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1227eb4cgab97g404ag98f7g43cf7d88551e" version="1">Devil's Bargain</content>
  <content contentuid="haea994f6g1a3dg4527g85edgbbc549666b7b" version="1">You made a deal with a fiend from one of the Nine Hells. You've been granted a devil's silver tongue, but it comes with a lead foot: You have advantage on all Charisma skill checks, but you have disadvantage on all Charisma saving throws. A piece of your soul has been lost forever.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0da64376gebf1g44beg8833gc8b838e77671" version="1">Gambler</content>
  <content contentuid="he3a75c40g20c1g4d71gb5d9g06704cc7bb76" version="1">You know when to hold them, when to fold them, when to walk away, and when to run. You are proficient in Deception, Sleight of Hand, and Insight.</content>
  <content contentuid="h50a06905g8947g4800gafa6g003db0377326" version="1">Gladiator</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c05c256g910fg44cegbda6g962b85dc507e" version="1">You fought for survival as a slave or possibly as a celebrity competitor. One way or another, you developed a proficiency for a variety of weapons to remain ready for what can be found in an arena: Clubs, daggers, handaxes, javelins, spears, scimitars, tridents, and even firearms. You know a good show can be critical to survival, and are proficient in Performance.</content>
  <content contentuid="h48845f89ge009g46b5g8f2ag3c29b90ad229" version="1">God-Touched</content>
  <content contentuid="hde1df695ga9efg4415gb182g151368b9a7e9" version="1">You had some form of direct interaction with a powerful deity in your past. The experience has gifted your mind with incredible fortitude, but enfeebled your physical form. You have advantage on Wisdom saving throws, but disadvantage on Constitution saving throws.</content>
  <content contentuid="h72114976g3e83g4410gb089gada97336cb63" version="1">Merchant</content>
  <content contentuid="hb73504e9g8a9dg473bg972eg768994d4d9f8" version="1">You made your coin by selling goods to the fair folk who frequented your stall. Sales are made on a combination of persuasion and marketing, and you are proficient in Persuasion and Deception. You also have a keen eye for details; you are proficient in Investigation and Perception.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5c30c07gfdb3g4382gb12fg826d0ed7d4d9" version="1">Pugilist</content>
  <content contentuid="h13650c7fgc43dg4b87gab09gf57d4d59d726" version="1">Fighting is not just your life but your career, with legal boxing matches and shady back alleys offering fame and fortune. Surviving as many rounds as you have confers proficiency in Atheltics and Acrobatics. Reading your opponent and entertaining a crowd has made you proficient in Insight and Performance.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1c253fe3294c4c3393a9374eee8166ea8cb4" version="1">Beatific Restoration</content>
  <content contentuid="hcaef727831364bcbac900084aaadecbcb717" version="1">Tap into your gift to replenish an expended spell slot of any level.</content>  
</contentList >